videoforums.co.uk 2014-02-12

# Video Editing Forums: Digital Director - VideoForums Privacy Policy

### What information do we collect? 

We collect information from you when you register on our site, respond to a survey or fill out a form. When registering on our site, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

>   * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
>   * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
>   * To send periodic emails
> 

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. 

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. 

### How do we protect your information? 

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

### Do we use cookies? 

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information 

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. 

> Our cookies help us: 
> 
>   * Make our website work as you'd expect 
>   * Save you having to login every time you visit the site 
>   * Remember your settings during and between visits 
>   * Offer you free services/content (thanks to advertising) 
>   * Improve the speed/security of the site 
>   * Allow you to share pages with social networks like Facebook 
>   * Personalise our site to you to help you get what you need faster 
>   * Continuously improve our website for you 
>   * Make our marketing more efficient (ultimately helping us to offer the service we do at the price we do) 
> 

We do not use cookies to: 

>   * Collect any personally identifiable information (without your express permission) 
>   * Collect any sensitive information (without your express permission) 
> 

Advertising Cookies Cookies are widely used in online advertising. Neither us, advertisers or our advertising partners can gain personally identifiable information from these cookies. We only work with advertising partners who work to accepted privacy standards such as http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/iab-good-practice-principles You can learn more about online advertising at http://www.youronlinechoices.com . You can opt-out of almost all advertising cookies at http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices although we would prefer that you didn’t as ultimately adverts help keep much of the internet free. It is also worth noting that opting out of advertising cookies will not mean you won't see adverts, just simply that they won't be tailored to you any longer. We use: DoubleClick - Privacy Policy owned by Google Banner Adverts We fund our site by showing adverts as you browse our site. These adverts are usually managed by a partner specialising in providing adverts for multiple sites. Invariably these partners place cookies to collect anonymous data about the websites you visits so they can personalise the adverts to you, ensure that you don't see the same adverts too frequently and ultimately report to advertisers on which adverts are working. Our partners include: Turning Cookies Off You can usually switch cookies off by adjusting your browser settings to stop it from accepting cookies (Learn how here). Doing so however will likely limit the functionality of our's and a large proportion of the world's websites as cookies are a standard part of most modern websites It may be that you concerns around cookies relate to so called "spyware". Rather than switching off cookies in your browser you may find that anti-spyware software achieves the same objective by automatically deleting cookies considered to be invasive. 

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties? 

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses 

### Terms and Conditions 

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.videoforums.co.uk/tos.php 

### Online Privacy Policy Only 

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

### Your Consent 

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. 

### Changes to our Privacy Policy 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. This policy was last modified on 02 July 2013 http://www.videoforums.co.uk
